<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<resources>
  <string name="ht_respect_nature_text">Respect in National Reserves and Parks
• Parks: protected areas. Frequent rules: stay on the trails, do not pick anything, no fire, dogs prohibited (even on a leash), drones prohibited unless authorized. Respect on-site signs and local orders.
• Nature reserves &amp; regional parks: variable rules (bivouac, dogs, fires). Check for seasonal quietness areas and signage.

Why not bathe in high-altitude lakes
• Fragile ecosystems: many lakes are oligotrophic and very sensitive; small disturbances have great effects.
• Pollutants: sunscreen/body products, textile fibres and micro-organisms degrade water and plankton; focus on managed bathing areas.
• Wildlife disturbance: amphibians and shorebirds are sensitive to noise, trampling and clapp (plants, spawning grounds).
• Health/safety: very cold water (thermal shock/hypothermia), slippery banks; Some municipalities prohibit bathing by decree.
• Simple rule: if a ban is displayed, you do not bathe; Otherwise, observe without entering the water, leave nothing, avoid prolonged contact.

Good practices in protected areas
• Stay on the trails to limit erosion.
• Bivouac: often tolerated overnight (after 7pm – before 9am), away from roads/houses; remain &gt; 20 m from lakes/water courses; leave with grey water and waste.
• Dogs: usually forbidden in park hearts; keep on a leash and respect periods of tranquillity.
• Drones: assimilated to motorized and prohibited aircraft in park cores (rare exceptions on authorization).
• Wildlife &amp; herds: do not continue; make a wide detour; Close the fences.

Marking: color codes
- GR: white/red; // = straight; angle = turn; Cross = wrong path.
GRP: yellow/red; territory loops.
PR: yellow; local/day loops.</string>
      <string name="pref_app_language_summary">Scegli la lingua dell'interfaccia.</string>
    <string name="pref_keep_screen_on_title">Schermo sempre acceso</string>
    <string name="pref_app_language_title">Lingua dell'app</string>
    <string name="pref_keep_screen_on_summary">Evita che lo schermo si spenga durante l'uso.</string>
</resources>
