<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<resources>
  <!-- Orages -->
  <string name="wx_thunder_title">Thunderstorms &amp; Lightning</string>
  <string name="wx_thunder_intro">Mountain thunderstorm = immediate danger (fouling, hail, gusts, flash floods). Anticipate and adapt the route.
.</string>
  <string name="wx_thunder_do">• Check the weather report before leaving (possible thunderstorm = short/evasive route).
• In the field, watch the sky: rapid budding, distant thunder, rotating wind, sizzling.
• Evacuate ridges, ridges, peaks, exposed slabs; target a low but dry area, away from an isolated point._TOK0__
• Step away from each other by at least 20 m to limit the group risk.
• As a last resort, squat on dry bag/cord (insulating), tight feet, minimum exposure time.
.</string>
  <string name="wx_thunder_dont">• Do not stay under an isolated tree, a metallic overhang, a top cross, an electric line.
• Do not use sticks/pilets held in the air; store antennas, masts, umbrellas.
• Do not shelter the entire group in the same place; avoid running caves and banks in flood.
.</string>
  <string name="wx_thunder_after">After the storm: prudence on wet snows/rocks, weakened snow bridges, flooded flows/locals.
.</string>
  <!-- Chaleur -->
  <string name="wx_heat_title">Heat &amp; sunshine</string>
  <string name="wx_heat_tips">• Early departure, adapted rhythm, frequent breaks in the shade.
• Drink before thirst, electrolytes if prolonged effort; hat + glasses category 3/4, cream SPF 50.\n
• Monitor headache, nausea, confusion: immediate cessation/refreshment; alert so worsening.
.</string>
  <!-- Froid -->
  <string name="wx_cold_title">Cold &amp; hypothermia</string>
  <string name="wx_cold_tips">• Overlay of layers (breathing/insulating/winding), hand/foot/head protections.
• Moulded = danger: prefer dry clothes; watch chills, malfeasance, drowsiness.\n
• Sweet hot drink, soil isolation (cover), shelter from the wind; Emergency alert if altered.
.</string>
  <!-- Vent -->
  <string name="wx_wind_title">Strong wind</string>
  <string name="wx_wind_tips">• Beware of gusts in ridges/coles, unstable cornices.
• Short-set poles, safe support points, dust glasses.
• Renunciate if uncertain progression: turn back = right decision.
.</string>
  </resources>
